"NETFLIX
オリジナルシリーズ"
（春雄(はるお)）飯も食べたし
After eating,
and a full day of playing games,
you must be tired right, Ono?
１日中対戦して疲れたろ
大野？
The old man's worried about you too.
爺やも心配してっから
もう帰らねーか？
Shouldn't we head back?
What's that face for?
なんだよその顔…
怒ってんの？
Are you upset?
I don't know what happened at your house,
家で何があったか
よく分かんねぇけど―
but you don't want to go home, then?
帰りたくねーってかい？
Jeez...
まったく…
帰りの電車賃まで
なくなった状況で―
You even played away the money for
your train fare home.
What were you planning to do?
どーするつもりだったのか…
I guess things back home
そこまでヤケになるくらい
家が嫌になっちまった
ってこったな…
were so unbearable, you got desperate.
Guess it can't be helped, then.
（春雄）しょうがねぇなぁ
Shall we go play a little more?
（春雄）
んじゃ もうちょっとだけ
遊びに行くか
え？
フンッ
♪〜
〜♪
（電話の呼び出し音）
（なみえ）はい…
Hello?
Oh, Haruo. Is everything okay?
あら 春雄
どうなった？
Oh, you found Akira?
え？　晶ちゃん 見つかった
In Kawasaki?
うん　川崎で？
Yeah, I found her but...
そう 見つかったのは
いいけどよ
Is something wrong?
（なみえ）何かあったの？
There's a bit of a problem, Mom.
うん ちょっと困ってんだ
おふくろ
Oh?
（なみえ）おろ？
お嬢様は帰りたくねぇって
頭突きしてくるし―
The princess is adamant about
not going home.
The last train already left, too.
終電は逃すしよ
（なみえ）まぁ 春雄ったら
高校生にもなって―
Goodness, Haruo.
You're in high school, but you're
so dependent on your mother. Oh, ho, ho!
お母さんに頼りきりなのね
ウヒョヒョヒョヒョ
Come on, could you be serious?
（春雄）なぁ マジメに
答えてくれよな〜
（なみえ）
ああん もう面倒だわねぇ…
Aw, what a pain.
えーとタウンページは
あったかしら
Let's see, where's the phone book...
アンタ
お金は持ってるわよね
You have money, right?
（春雄）一応…
（電話ボックスの開く音）
５分後にもっかい
かけ直せってよ
She asked me call her back
in five minutes.
Sounds like
she'll figure out a way for us.
おふくろが何かしてくれる
らしいぜ
何考えてんのか
わかんねーけど…
I'm not sure what she has in mind.
Either way, you're one troublesome lady.
それにしても
困ったお嬢様だよ お前は
Running away is one thing,
but you were reckless with no plan.
家出したはいいが
まるで無計画で無鉄砲だし
野宿でもする気だったんか？
You planned to sleep on the streets?
People say you're gifted,
秀才と言われたオマエでも
but as for common sense,
you're a bigger fool than me.
そういうトコ
俺よりバカだよなぁ
A violent, stubborn idiot--
バカでボーリョク的で
オタンコナ…
（衝撃音）
バカでボーリョク的で
オタンコナ…
（衝撃音）
（晶）くっ！
あいっ！
Mom...
（春雄）おふくろ
宿をとるならとるで―
If you were getting us a hotel,
you should've rented two rooms!
２つ部屋を
用意してくれりゃいいのに…
おい 本当に大丈夫か？
Hey, you sure you're okay with this?
お前を連れ回したと
勘違いされて―
Your family won't misunderstand
I brought you here, right?
黒服が来たり
しねーだろうな？
Men in black suits won't show up
はたまた誘拐の疑惑を
かけられたりよ…
assuming I kidnapped you, will they?
（晶）はぁ…
What?
（春雄）えええ〜
You think they actually might?
可能性あるかも
しんねえのかよ
We'll deal with it if it happens, I guess.
まぁ その時はその時だ
無口なお前の
必死な弁解を信じてるぜ
I'll put faith in your quiet
but frantic excuses.
Regardless, I'm relieved.
なんにせよ ホッとしたよ
（ゲーム音）
The city can get really dangerous
at night.
（ゲーム音）
深夜の街はいろいろと
アブなそーだからな
This relief is almost akin to
finding a save point, isn't it?
この安堵感は―
セーブポイントに
辿り着いた時とよく似てるぜ
なぁ？
I guess you wouldn't know
as you don't own a home console.
あ ワカンネーか
家庭用の持ってね〜し…
Why do you look so angry?
なんなんだよ
ムスーッとして
やっぱ帰るか？
Would you rather go home, then?
（晶）ん…
んんんんんん！
That so?
あ そう　んじゃ
コッチとソッチ―
Then this one or that one?
Let's decide where we'll sleep.
どっちで寝たいか決めようぜ
I don't mind either.
オレはどっちでもいいけど
そうだな…
Although...
こっちの窓際だと―
the window-side would be the first
a ghost would attack.
オバケに最初に
襲われそうだし…
（晶）！？
オバケに最初に
襲われそうだし…
But a murderer would probably
kill the person door-side, first.
そっちだと出入口から
入ってきた―
殺人鬼に
やられちまいそうだな…
（叩く音）
痛い 痛い 冗談だっての！
（晶）ふーん　いー
Ow, ow, it was just a joke!
（叩く音）
相も変わらずお化け嫌いか
You're as much of a scaredy-cat as ever.
（晶）ふーん　いー
（戸を開ける音）
まあ どっちで寝るかは
ともかく
Well, putting aside the question
of which bed,
風呂沸かすべ  風呂
I'm going to draw a bath.
It goes without saying, but I'm exhausted.
（春雄）
今日はさすがにクタクタだぜ
Once it's drawn, you go first.
沸いたらお前 先に入れよ
（湯が出る音）
Oh, is this one of those
western bathrooms?
（湯が出る音）
これってあれ
ユニットバスなの？
頭洗う時どうすんだ？
How do you wash your hair?
オレが入るときまたお湯を
溜(た)め直すってことか？
Do I have to re-draw the bath,
before I take one?
（ＣＭ）
カステラをあんこで挟んだ
べた焼きっ！
The sticky roll of sponge cake in red
bean paste will make your hands sticky!
手がべたべたするーっ！
RED BEANS GROWN 100% IN JAPAN!
甘〜い
It's so sweet!
（春雄）土曜の深夜は何も
面白いもんやってないな…
There's nothing good on TV
on Saturday nights.
（春雄）土曜の深夜は何も
面白いもんやってないな…
なんだこの状況
What is this situation?
I haven't seen Ono in so long,
久しぶりに
大野に会ったのに―
なんでイキナリ
こんな所にいるんだよ
but we're suddenly at a place like this.
She hasn't said anything
in this cramped room.
この狭い部屋で―
ウンともスンとも
言わねーしな…
I can't calm down.
落ち着かねーから
額の裏でも見てみよう…
I'll take a look
at the back of this picture.
うおっ！
Whoa!
Oh, it's just Shaman-kan.
（春雄）なんだ ただの
シャーマンカーンか…
はぁ
（戸が開く音）
Oh.
おっ！
（春雄）高校に入ってから
すでに４ヶ月か…
It's already been four months
since we started high school.
積りに積もった話が
あったはずなんだけどなぁ…
There should've been plenty of things
for us to catch up on.
Hmm, getting in a bathtub next to
the toilet feels strange.
うーん
便所の横で風呂に入るって
妙な気分だなぁ…
And the curtain goes in the water?
カーテンって湯船に
入れておくんだな…
大野が教えてくれなきゃ
わかんなかったぜ…
If Ono hadn't told me,
I wouldn't have known.
（ＣＭ音楽）
This sticky roll of sponge cake
in red bean paste
（ＣＭ）
カステラをあんこで挟んだ
べた焼きっ！
手がべたべたするーっ！
will make your hands sticky!
甘〜い！
It's so sweet!
（春雄）深夜のテレビは―
Late night TV just keeps broadcasting
the same commercial over and over.
同じＣＭを
繰り返し放送するんだな
（ＴＶＣＭ）
高級ブランドメガネの
品ぞろえが抜群？
（ＴＶＣＭ）
高級ブランドメガネの
品ぞろえが抜群？
（ＴＶＣＭ）
高級ブランドメガネの
品ぞろえが抜群？
見てておかしくなりそうだぜ
I feel I'm going crazy watching this.
しかも全品大安売り！
メガネのことなら
I can't think of what to talk about.
（春雄）間がもたねェ
せめてこの部屋に
スト２
If only Street Fighter II,
or Champion Edition,
及びダッシュ
及びターボ
or Hyper Fighting, or the New Challengers
were in this room!
及びスト２Ｘが
存在してくれたなら…
I know!
そーだ！
Does this TV have a video input?
このテレビに
ビデオ入力端子があるか否か
It does! This'll work, Ono!
あるある！
イケるぜ 大野！
It's time to break out the NES I bought
before we ate.
さっき飯を食った後に
購入した―
ニューファミコンの出番だぜ
そしてこれは―
And this game bestowed upon me
by an angel!
店主がオマケに
つけてくれたソフトだっ！
旧ファミコンが
ぶっ壊れてたから―
My Super Nintendo suddenly broke,
今日買って正解だったぜ
so it was good I bought this today.
FINAL FANTASY
ソフトはそもそも
The label is messed up, so you can't tell
what game it is
ラベルが剥(は)がれてて
何のゲームかも分からんが…
but I'm sure it's not Final Fantasy.
絶対ファイナル･
ファンタジーじゃねェな
The cartridge is the wrong color.
カセットも色が違うし
（カセット挿入音）
Oh!
（春雄）おおっ！
DOWNTOWN NEKKETSU KOUSHINKYOKU
（ゲーム音）
SOREYUKE DAIUNDOKAI
I can't believe it's Daiundokai.
まさか大運動会とはな
超名作じゃねェか
This game is famous.
You don't know it?
That's so like you.
知らねェのか？
さすがはお嬢様だ
In this action game, teams face off
in a sports meet.
こいつはチーム対抗で
運動会を戦う―
アクションゲームだ
It's called a "sports meet" but it's not
a normal meet.
運動会って言っても
競技は普通じゃなくて
町内クロスカントリーとか
格闘大会なんかもあるんだ
There's a cross-country race in the city,
and even a fighting match.
And of course, you can interfere
with opposing teams
もちろん競技中に
敵チームの妨害もアリだぜ
（晶）んふ…
ウズウズしてきたようだな
Looks like you're itching to start.
しかしこんな深夜に―
I never thought I'd be up late night
playing Daiundokai with you.
お前と大運動会に
興(きょう)じるなんてな
It's a little surreal.
何だか不思議だよ
（ゲーム音）
You're okay playing as Hanazono, right?
大野は“はなぞの”で
いいよな？
I'll be Nekketsu.
俺は“ねっけつ”だ
この競技は町内を
走り続ける競争だ
In this game, we compete by running
through the city.
（晶）…？
（春雄）
突然他人の家に入って
戸惑ってるようだな…
She's rattled after suddenly entering
someone's house.
（春雄）こいつは
ただの競争じゃねえぜ
This is no ordinary race!
（晶）！？
I told you, you could interfere
with other players.
妨害ありって言ったろ
Hey, I can't get through!
（春雄）
おいっ！
通れねーだろーがよ
（晶）ふーん
あぁー　息がぁぁ！
Ugh, I'm gonna drown!
（ゲーム音）
（春雄）
完全にゲームに慣れてやがる
She's completely adapted to the game.
（春雄）
ファミコンだって―
I guess the NES still has loads
of playable games.
まだまだ遊べるゲームは
いくらでもあるんだな…
But I want you to see how amazing
the next generation consoles are.
けど 大野に次世代機の―
とてつもなさを
見せてやりてーよ
The arcade ports alone are
just incredible.
ゲーセンゲームの移植が
とにかくスゴイんだ
It almost makes me pity you
for not being able to get a home console.
家庭用ゲーム機を
買ってもらえないお前が―
不憫(ふびん)に思えるくらいな…
When will those stiff, suffocating lessons
of yours be over?
いつになったら―
お前んちの堅っ苦しい
躾(しつけ)ってヤツが終わるんだ？
If not for that, you could enjoy games
at your leisure.
んなもんなけりゃ
気兼ねなく
ゲームが楽しめるのに…
If only there was something I could do...
俺が何かできればなぁ…
（ゲーム音）
（晶）！？
Oh.
（春雄の寝息）
（春雄）おお…　おお？
I wasn't sure where I was for a second.
一瞬どこかと思ったぜ
なんでオレも大野も
ベッドの逆向きで寝てんだ？
Why are Ono and I both sleeping backwards
on the bed?
Oh, good morning.
おっ　おはようございます
Ono, I forgot to mention this
（春雄）大野
いい忘れちまったが オレ
but I have to go to my part-time job
this morning.
これから朝のバイトに
行かなきゃいかんのよ…
I work from 6:30 to 11:00 a.m.
今日は６時半から
11時までの労働でさ
It's still 6 a.m., right?
まだ６時だろ
チェックアウトは12時だから
お前はまだ寝てていいぞ
Check out is at noon,
so you can sleep some more.
I'll come back here before noon.
12時前にはまたオレ
ここに帰ってくるからよ
あとこれ
お金ここに置いておくからな
And I'll leave some money here.
If you get hungry, buy something
at the shop downstairs.
お腹すいたら下のコンビニで
買うといいぜ
（戸を開ける音）
（春雄）
んじゃ　行ってくるな…
Well, I'll be leaving.
（足音）
（春雄）大野のやつ
I'm sure Ono will get chewed out real bad
when she gets home.
今日家に帰ったら
こっぴどく
怒られるんだろうな…
（春雄）ああ…
I want to be there for her.
（春雄）アイツの支えに
なってやりてェな
（春雄）ふん！
ういいい　う…
（おはちゃん）
あらあ矢口君―
Oh, Yaguchi. You're more motivated
than usual today.
今日はいつになく
気合入ってるわね
（春雄）うーん
（春雄）ひぃ…　ひぃ…
（戸を開ける音）
ア…
Ready to go home?
（春雄）帰るか
You might get in trouble
for staying out until the morning.
（春雄）
お嬢様が朝帰りした
ってことでとがめられるかも
But...
だけどよ
My mom said she'd explain the situation
おふくろも事情を
説明してくれるって―
言ってたし
俺も爺やによく話しとくよ
and I'll tell the old man everything, too.
Well, if things get unbearable at home
again, you can come by anytime.
まぁ
また家のことで嫌になったら
ウチに来いや
The Yaguchi house will always be
your refuge.
矢口家がいつでも
匿(かくま)ってやるぜ
Just enduring all the time
can be harmful, Ono.
（春雄）
あんまり耐えてばっかだと
毒だぜ 大野
Whoa! What is it?
おわっ　おい何だよ
What's that?
アレが何だ？
Those new photo booths?
最近でた
プリント倶楽部だろ？
You want to take one?
撮りてェーのか？
（撮影音）
It takes your picture then prints it
as a sticker, right?
写真撮られて
シールになるやつだよな
This is definitely a machine
geared for girls.
いかにも女ウケしそうな
機械だが…
（春雄）照れくせェ
How embarrassing...
But not if I make a weird face!
変な顔してごまかそう
（晶）！
（衝撃音）
こーゆー事は耐えろや
I promised myself I'd put up with
this stuff.
You big jerk.
アホたれ
♪
（ゲーム音）
Such tricky movement!
（男Ａ）
なんつートリッキーな動きだ
（男Ｂ）
あんな動きをされたら―
With movement like that,
you really don't want to approach
with a jump.
空中戦に
持ち込む気が起きねェ…
（男Ｃ）うおおおっ！
空中ガードキャンセルッ！
Ah, aerial blocking!
This girl is something else!
（男Ａ）半端ねェ女子だぜ
（男Ｂ）乱入する事を
躊躇(ちゅうちょ)させられる…
She makes me hesitate to take my turn.
It's been about a year and a half
（小春）矢口君と出会って
初めてアーケードゲームを
触って約１年半
since I met Yaguchi and learned
to play my first game.
I'd never had any interests,
無趣味だった私が
こんなにも夢中になるなんて
so I never imagined I'd become
so engrossed in something.
思いもよらなかった
この世界を教えてくれた
矢口君には感謝でいっぱい…
I'm so grateful to Yaguchi for showing me
this world.
それからというもの…
Since then, I've worked hard
to become his equal
彼と対等になるため
努力してきたけど
but no matter how high I climb,
どんなに登りつめても
the reason why the distance between us
never shrinks,
一向に矢口君との距離が
縮まらないのは
is because Yaguchi only sees her
in his eyes.
やっぱり 矢口君には
あの人しか見えてないから
ハァ…
（小春）
出るのはため息ばかり
All I've done is sigh...
（男Ｃ）出た！
ファイナルガーディアンッ！
There it is! The final guardian!
（ゲーム音）
Over at 14 wins?
（小春）
14連勝で終わったか…
なんだかなぁ
I can do better.
Excuse me.
（ゲーマーＡ）あの
You're really good.
ハンターめっちゃ
上手いっすね
ホンット上手いっすね
Like really good.
Huh, what?
（小春）えっ 何？
Are you by yourself right now?
（ゲーマーＡ）
今 一人っすか？
（小春）あ…
If you'd like, why don't you catch some
prizes with me at the claw machine?
（ゲーマーＡ）
もしよかったら―
一緒にＵＦＯで
景品をキャッチしませんか
アナタは台の側面から
覗(のぞ)いていただき
I want you to watch me,
ベストポイントでストップと
言ってほしいのです
and tell me when to stop
and drop the claw.
What? That's cheating.
（小春）何よそのインチキ
If it were Yaguchi, he'd skip straight
to the challenge.
矢口君だったらそんな事せず
まっすぐ距離感に挑むはずよ
（春雄）よぉー 日高ァー
Hey, Hidaka.
あっ
Are you here to make the veteran guys
cry again?
今日も強豪プレーヤーの
男達を泣かせに来たか？
Yaguchi!
矢口君
H-Huh? You have a boyfriend?
な なんだ　彼氏持ちか
逃げよっ
-Time to bail.
-Huh?
（春雄）ん？
お友達？
Friend of yours?
Boyfriend?
（小春）彼氏
（春雄）
もうすぐ２が出るから
Tekken II is coming soon but I have to
practice with Tekken I while I can.
１も今のうちに
やり込まないとな
I like Virtua, but Tekken is
one of my favorites!
バーチャも好きだけど
鉄拳も大好物だぜ
He's like a kid.
（小春）子供っぽいなぁ…
Even now, I can't imagine what goes on
in his mind.
今でも 何考えてるか
全然わからない…
He gets so engrossed in the game,
ゲームに没頭しすぎてて
it's like I don't even exist.
私なんか
まるで眼中にない感じ…
But still, even though Yaguchi
is engrossed in his own world,
それでも―
己の世界に真っ直ぐな
矢口君に―
I'm stlll attracted to him.
私は
惹(ひ)かれちゃってるんだなぁ…
（神崎）うお？
Huh?
何考えてんだコイツはっ？
What's this guy thinking?
（小春）常に何を見てるか
分かる人って
There's a comfort in knowing
what he's always looking at.
安心できるんだよね
あと意外と優しいし…
He's surprisingly kind, too.
Crap! He doesn't have a shred
of kindness!
（台を叩く音）
くそっ！
優しさのカケラもねェ
Hey, Hidaka.
やい 日高っ！
いつになったら俺に
リベンジさせてくれるんだよ
When are you gonna let me
get revenge for before.
Let's settle it once and for all.
いい加減
白黒つけようやっ！
Not today.
今日はイヤッ
さっきの14連勝で
気が抜けちゃった
That 14-streak took the wind
out of my sail.
（春雄）この野郎〜
You little...
じゃあ俺は28連勝して―
Then I'll go get a 28-win streak,
乱入してきた仕事帰りの
サラリーマン達を―
and make the businessmen
on their way home cry like babies!
泣かせてやるっ！
（ゲーム）
ん！　ん！　おりゃー！
ん！　ん！　はい！！
（ゲーム）ＫＯ
うわああ！！
どうだっ！　ムキになった
オレに挑む者は皆
How's that?
Now that I've made my comeback,
I'll slice any and all challengers
into sashimi!
刺し身にしてやるぜっ！
（春雄）
ぐっ！　ぐぐ あああ…
（ゲーム）ＫＯ
Sasquatch's dash into middle punch leads
into too many chain combos!
サスカッチの前ダッシュ中
パンチが刺さったあとの―
チューンコンボがハンパねぇ
How can you guard after...
（小春）あーあ 最近
対戦ゲームばかりだなぁ
上ガードなのか
下ガードなのかワケわからん
It's been all fighting games, lately.
Sometimes I want to sit next to him
and play Puzzle Bubble, too.
たまには肩を並べて―
バズルボブルとか
やりたいのに…
That's right.
Today's the firework festival.
（なみえ）今日は
花火大会だったわね
Are you going, Haruo?
春雄は行かないの？
No, I'm not.
（春雄）行かん 行かん
I get tired of that stuff after watching
for about ten seconds.
オレはアレ10秒くらい見て
すぐ飽きちまうんだよな
What? You have no romantic bone
in your body.
（なみえ）アラ
全然ロマンティックの
欠片もないんだから
Don't you have someone to go with?
一緒に行く人はいないの？
What about that Akira Ono?
大野の晶ちゃんとか
どうなの？
さそってみなさいよ
Why don't you ask her.
うるさいなぁ おふくろは
Leave me alone, Mom.
Oh, but you two shared
a good morning kiss!
あら 朝チュンした仲なのに
意地を張るの？
You have to tell me about
your youthful experiences!
青春話をお母さんにも
聞かせてちょうだいよ
何言ってんだよ まったく
Jeez, what are you talking about?
I heard later from the old man
that they were pretty upset with her.
あのあと爺やに聞いたけど
かなり怒られたらしいぜ
But thanks to your help,
the punishment wasn't as severe.
おふくろの
フォローのおかげで―
手は上げられなかった
らしいけど…
No matter if it's some family policy,
あんまり
家の方針だからって―
娘に教養を押し付けるのも
どうかと思うわね
I'm not sure I agree with forcing lessons
on your daughter.
I hope they revise this family policy
after this runaway incident.
（なみえ）
家出事件がキッカケで―
少しは方針とやらが
改善されたらいいけど
春雄
Haruo, the next time you see her,
be good to her again.
あの子と会ったら
また優しくしてあげなさいよ
うん
Yeah.
（チャイムの音）
Oh, coming!
（なみえ）は〜い
（春雄）今日も大野
ゲーセンにいなかったな
-Ono wasn't at the arcade today.
-Oh, Koharu!
（春雄）今日も大野
ゲーセンにいなかったな
（戸を開ける音）
（春雄）今日も大野
ゲーセンにいなかったな
（戸を開ける音）
（なみえ）
あら 小春ちゃん
（春雄）今日も大野
ゲーセンにいなかったな
（なみえ）
あら 小春ちゃん
電話ってのもなぁ
-Even if I were to...
-Yes, he's here.
電話ってのもなぁ
even if she answered,
would she talk?
アイツが出たとしても
会話になるかどうか…
（なみえ）春雄？
お上がんなさい
アイツが出たとしても
会話になるかどうか…
（小春）おじゃまします
Sorry to intrude.
Huh?
あ？
Oh!
（春雄）あ！？
ひ 日高っ！　なんだよ
そのプレステは？
H-Hidaka. What's that PlayStation for?
まさかオレにくれる…
Are you giving it to me?
（小春）
あげるわけないでしょ　もう
Of course not.
I'm letting you borrow it.
貸してあげようと思ったの
Didn't you say earlier,
昼間に言ってたでしょ
that you wanted to practice Tekken since
Tekken II was coming out?
もうすぐ鉄拳２が出るから
鉄拳１をやりこみたいって
If you have the PlayStation and the game,
you could practice, right?
プレステ本体と
ソフトがあれば―
今のうちに
予習しとけるでしょ
言ったっけなそういえば…
I did, didn't I?
So you brought it all the way here for me?
で わざわざ
持ってきてくれたんか？
Yeah, nice of me right?
うん 優しいでしょ
（なみえ）
うちの息子が最近―
Why has the female presence in
my son's life suddenly increased?
（なみえ）
うちの息子が最近―
（春雄）あ ハイ
女っけが多くなったのは
なぜ？
（春雄）おおおおっ！
Ohh!
So this is the PlayStation!
これが
プレイステーション！
（春雄）あっ ぎぎ
サターン派である
オレにとっては―
As a Saturn fan, this is my first time
touching the real thing.
実物を触るのは初めてだぜ
This is the controller?
こんな
コントローラだったのか
I never thought this day would come!
とうとうこの日が来るとは
私の家にやりに来なよって
言っても―
When I said you could come play it
at my place, you weirdly refused.
変に遠慮(えんりょ)してたんじゃない
（春雄）おおっ！
Whoa, I can play Tekken at home!
家で鉄拳ができるっ！
I haven't been this moved since Virtua.
（春雄）
バーチャ以来の感動だ
このプレステコントローラの
Pressing multiple buttons on this
PlayStation controller looks tough.
ボタン同時押しってのが
シビアだな
こうして押せば良いのか
Should I push them like this?
こうして押せば良いのか？
Or like this?
オレが使うキングは―
I use King, who relies
on simultaneous inputs.
ボタン同時押しが
基本だからな
How do you do it, Hidaka?
日高はどうやってたよ？
（小春）そんな事
意識したことないな
I don't really think about that stuff.
Hidaka, play with me.
日高ぁ 対戦してみようぜ
白黒対決とか関係なしに
遊びで少し…
Just for fun. It won't affect
our grudge match.
（小春）いいよ いいよ
No, thanks.
3D games aren't my thing.
３Ｄ系のゲームはあんまり
得意じゃないんだよね…
I prefer watching them from behind.
私はうしろで見てるほうが
好き
Huh?
（春雄）ほえー
Huh, the Saturn? You'll lend it to me?
（小春）あ サターン？
貸してくれるの？
Sure, if you lend me the PlayStation,
I have to lend you mine.
おうよ
プレステ貸してくれんなら
こっちも貸さんとな
ソフトはバーチャと
デイトナＵＳＡと―
The games I have are Virtua, Daytona USA,
日高が好きそうなＤの食卓
and D, which I'm sure you'll like.
Will you play them?
やるよな
うん　やる
Yeah, I will.
Then, hold on a minute.
んじゃ ちょっと待ってろ
I'll go find a bag downstairs.
下で紙袋さがしてくっからよ
うん
Okay.
Mom, are there any
old bags lying around here?
（春雄）おふくろー
袋あるー？
（なみえ）はー？
ダジャレー？
Huh, was that a joke?
Yaguchi's desk...
（小春）矢口君の机…
It's so cluttered.
かなり乱雑としてる
高校に入ってから
勉強してるのかな…？
Has he studied since he started
high school?
Well, considering it's Yaguchi...
まぁ 矢口君のことだから…
あっ！
Oh!
♪
What are you doing, Haruo?
（なみえ）
何やってんのよ 春雄！
Making a lady walk home alone after dark?
夜道をレディー１人で
帰らせる気？
What an inconsiderate boy!
気が利かない子だわね
まったく！
（平手打ちの音）
あいで！
Ow!
（小春）
すぐ近くだからいいのに
You didn't have to, I live close by.
（春雄）いやいや
It's fine.
（小春）今夜は
花火大会なんだよね
Tonight's the firework festival, right?
Yeah. but I'm not really interested.
（春雄）うん
まあオレは全然興味がない
Ah, I see.
あ そう…
（春雄）ん？
Hmm?
By the way, on August 11th,
そういえば８月11日にさ
ストリートファイターの
実写映像版がでるんだよね
Street Fighter: The Movie is coming out.
Have you heard?
知ってっか？
Van Damme is playing Guile.
ヴァン･ダムがガイル役で
出てる映画
The live-action version
of Street Fighter II.
その実写取り込みのスト２
Now that you've lent me your PlayStation,
プレステを貸してもらった今
プレステ版を買うか―
I'm not sure whether to buy the PS version
or the Saturn one--
サターン版を買うか迷っててよ
Yaguchi.
矢口君
ん？　なに？
Huh, what is it?
A-Are you and Ono dating?
大野さんとは
付き合ってるの？
Huh? We're not dating.
えっ
付き合ってないけど…
How do you feel...
矢口君は大野さんのこと
どう思ってるの？
about Ono?
ど…　どう思ってる…
H-How do I feel?
Do you like her?
好き？
Why are you suddenly talking
about "liking"?
なんだよイキナリ…
好き？って
If you mean her gaming skill and devotion,
アイツのゲームの腕とか
姿勢はその
スゲー好きだけど…
then I really like those.
異性として…
What about as a girl?
Gir...
い…
私は矢口君の事が好き
I... like you, Yaguchi.
♪〜
I love you!
大好き
-Hidaka--
-Don't say anything!
（春雄）ひ 日高…
何も言わないで！
（衝撃音）
（小春）何も言わないで
恥ずかしいから
Don't say anything, it's embarrassing!
オ オレのサターンで…
W-With my own Saturn...
Sorry. Yaguchi, I'm sorry.
ごめん 矢口君 ごめん…
一方的なのはわかってる
I know it's one-sided...
I know Ono is a big part of your life.
矢口君にとって
大野さんが
大きな存在だってのも
分かってる
I know there's no room
to come between you guys.
二人の関係は―
他人が入り込む
余地がなさそうなのも分かる
それでも…
Even so...
私は矢口君のことが好き
I still like you.
If it's come to this, I'll get serious.
こうなったら強硬手段
前々から言われてた
矢口君との再戦
The rematch you've been talking about
for so long...
その勝負で矢口君が勝ったら
If you win the match,
私はおとなしく引き下がる
I'll back down quietly.
But, if...
で もし…
私が勝ったなら
If I win...
Go out with me.
私とつきあって
〜♪
Subtitle translation by
Emily Noguchi
♪〜
〜♪